https://www.vyapin.com/company/privacypolicy

Privacy Policy - Vyapin Software Systems Pvt Ltd
Free Trial Questions?
North America: +1 (646) 257-3449
Global: +91-44-2471 7142
Support Hours (M - F): 9am - 8pm IST (GMT+5:30)
PRODUCTS  SharePoint SharePoint Migration SharePoint Archive & Restore SharePoint Export SharePoint Metadata Manager SharePoint Governance & Reporting SharePoint Data Integration SharePoint Security Reporting (App)
Office 365 Office 365 Migrator Office 365 Archiver Office 365 Reports Office 365 Manager Office 365 Migration Planner
Windows Windows Infrastructure Audit – Windows Reports – Azure Reports – Hyper-V Reports
NTFS Security Management Suite – NTFS Security Auditor – NTFS Change Auditor – NTFS Security Manager
Active Directory Active Directory Change Audit Active Directory Reports
Exchange Exchange Audit & Reporting
IIS ARK for IIS Download Free Trial Now
SUPPORT  Contact Tech Support Software Feature Request Software Maintenance Software Registration Software Upgrade PURCHASE  SharePoint Dockit Migrator Dockit Archiver SharePoint Governance & Reporting SPListX for SharePoint Dockit Metadata Manager External Data Connector for SharePoint
Office 365 Office 365 Migrator Office 365 Archiver Office 365 Reports Office 365 Manager Office 365 Migration Planner
Windows ARK for Windows Enterprise – Windows Reports – Azure Reports – Hyper-V Reports
NTFS Security Management Suite – NTFS Security Auditor – NTFS Change Auditor – NTFS Security Manager
Active Directory Active Directory Change Tracker ARK for Active Directory
Exchange ARK for Exchange Server
IIS ARK for IIS Request For Quote
RESOURCES  Case Studies Data Sheets Downloads Newsletter Knowledge Base Online Help User Manuals White Papers COMPANY  Alliances Customers Customer Testimonials Partners And Resellers Privacy Policy Careers Contact Us BLOG
Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy document provides you with information on how we collect and process your personal data through the use of Vyapin website.Vyapin Software Systems (Vyapin) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information.Vyapin is a data controller. This means that we are responsible for deciding how we hold and use personal information about you.Contact InformationVyapin Software Systems Private Limited2A, “K. G. Sunshine”, No. 48, 12th AvenueAshok Nagar, Chennai – 600083, Indiasupport@vyapin.com+91-44-2471 7142General Privacy StatementVyapin respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use its products and services. Vyapin welcomes you to visit the website without providing any personal information. However, to access some areas of the site and also to get in touch with Vyapin related to its products and services, user registration is required. Vyapin may occasionally use your email to provide you with periodic product and service information and updates. However, you can choose to opt out of these mailings using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all the mails you receive or by submitting a data change or removal request from our website. Any additional information you provide is optional and remains personal and confidential.Vyapin’s privacy policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Vyapin’s control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.What is Personal Information?Personal information is stated as “any information about a recognizable individual”. This may comprise, for example, email addresses and contact details and any related information provided to Vyapin in the progression of its business operations, or which Vyapin may obtain from business inquiries. Personal information that is collected and cannot be connected with a distinguishable individual is not considered to be personal information.We may disclose or share your private information provided by you to our partners, re-sellers, other technology platforms or technology providers (such as email systems, third-party plugins on Vyapin website), business service providers who assist us in our sales, support, marketing and promotional activities (such as marketing communication companies, distributors, resellers and so on). See section on how we may share your information for legitimate purposes during the normal course of our business.What Personal Information do we collect and how we collect and use it?Vyapin collects and uses personal information in several different ways as mentioned below:Website Data – When users visit and use our website for certain purposesVyapin collects personal information such as users’ name, e-mail address, phone number and other related contact information from users when using our website for purposes such as the following:Making a pre-sale or post-sale inquiry about Vyapin’s products & servicesDownloading our software products for evaluation or purchaseDownloading documents related to our productsWhen requesting license keys for our software productsSubmit a request or an order for a Vyapin trial and/or productRequest Technical supportContact Vyapin for any other purpose from the websiteSign up to receive Vyapin’s newsletters, e-books etc.Communication Data – When users communicate with usThis includes information provided by Users when communicating to us.The data we collect from any Communication includes any communication that you send us through a contact form on our website, through email, text, chat service on our sites, social media messaging, social media posting or communication in any other form. We process this data for the purposes of communicating with you, for record keeping and for other legal and regulatory purposes.Technical DataWhile users visiting the website, Vyapin may collect depersonalized information such as cookies, technical information using electronic means. This includes information about visits to the website, IP address of the users’ computer, website url from which the user came, etc. This data is used to find out and enhance the usefulness of the website, improve the experience for users, improve our marketing and grow our business. If this information relates to an identifiable individual, Vyapin will treat this information as personal information.Customer DataCustomer Data includes all data related to the purchase of Vyapin products and/or services such as your name, title, billing address, delivery address, email address, phone number, contact details, purchase details and so on. We process this data to fulfill your purchase and to keep records of such transactions.What other information do we collect?Information using Cookies and user choiceUsers can restrict the use of cookies by enabling the settings in their browser. The “Help” option in all browsers will guide users on how to avoid accepting new cookies, how to notify the users when they receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies completely.https://www.wikihow.com/Disable-CookiesGoogle Analytics DataVyapin uses Google Analytics which permits it to view information on user website actions such as page views, source and time spent on our website, etc. This information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning that it cannot be tracked back to individuals. Users may opt-out of Vyapin’s use of Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out add-on in their browsers.https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptoutHow we may share your personal information?Vyapin may grant access to personal information with our partners, re-sellers, web hosting, business service providers and technology service providers in order to conduct our business operations efficiently. Such third parties may be located anywhere in the world. The third parties with whom we share your personal information are:Resellers and Distributors who assist us in selling our products.Partners who promote, sell, market and support our products and servicesTechnology Service providers who provide IT, support and system administration services.Business Service providers such as sales and marketing communication companies.Professionals including auditors, lawyers and bankers.Government bodies that require us to report processing activities.We require all third parties with whom we share your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We share such information with such third parties only for specific purposes and only to the extent necessary.Marketing, Sales and Support CommunicationsWe may send you marketing, sales or technical support related communications if (a) you made a purchase or requested information from us about our products or services or electronically downloaded our products for evaluation by filling out forms on our website or (b) you opted in to receive marketing communications. You may opt out of receiving marketing emails from us at any time.For example, once you electronically download our product for evaluation or purchase or when you contact us requesting information about any of our products, we will always communicate with you further with any other additional information related to technical support or sales that may be useful to you. Any such communication may include one or more of the following: (a) support information that is of technical nature, (b) information about other related products, (c) information about current sales promotions (d) information related to product licensing schemes, (e) pricing information and purchase instructions for the products.If you opt out of receiving marketing communications this opt-out does not apply to personal data provided to us as part of becoming our customers (such as purchasing our products or services, maintenance and support contracts).How we retain your data?We will retain your data as long as it is necessary for us to fulfill all our legal and regulatory obligations. If you are our customer or had been a customer at some point in time, we will retain your data in order for us to fulfill our legal, accounting and reporting requirements. If you are not our customer and were not a customer at any point in time, we will retain your data to the extent necessary for our records as per the terms of this privacy policy.How to Opt-Out or Request for Data Change or Removal?You can initiate a request to update your information, unsubscribe from our mailing list or to remove your data (only if you are not a customer of Vyapin). We will address your request as early as possible and you will be notified about the status of your request by e-mail.By using Vyapin website, you consent to the collection and use of information as we have outlined in this policy and any relevant Terms of Use.Vyapin may decide to change this policy from time to time. Changes in this Privacy Policy would be posted on Vyapin website.
SOLUTIONSMigrationArchiveSecurityManagementAuditRESOURCESCase StudiesData SheetsDownloadsKnowledge BaseNewsletterOnline HelpUser ManualsWhite PapersSUPPORTContact Tech SupportSoftware Feature RequestSoftware MaintenanceSoftware RegistrationSoftware UpgradeCOMPANYAlliancesCustomersCustomer TestimonialsPartners And ResellersCareersContact UsAbout Us
COMPANYPURCHASESUPPORTBLOGPRIVACY POLICYUNSUBSCRIBESITE MAP Copyright ©
Vyapin Software Systems (P) Ltd.All rights reserved.
TwitterFacebookLinkedinYouTube
^
